The job of a convolutional neural network is to discover patterns contained in an image.
卷积神经网络的职责是发现图像中的图案
A sequence of layers is responsible for this discovery.
我们使用一系列层级发现这些图案
The layers in a CNN convert an input image array into
CNN 中的层级会将输入图像数组
a representation that encodes only the content of the image.
变成只包含图像内容的表示法
This is often called a feature level representation of an image or a feature vector.
这通常称为图像的特征级表示法 或称为特征向量
It may be helpful to think about it like this,
为了帮助理解 举个例子
take two input images that are both images of a car.
假设有两张汽车图像
Both are very different,
它们差别很大
and if I was to frame these pictures,
如果我要描述这些图像
the detail would be what makes them stylistically interesting.
肯定会考虑细节风格之类的
But for an image classifier,
但是对于图像分类器来说
it only wants to know that these are both images of cars.
它只想知道这两张图像都是汽车图像
When you look at how these images are transformed
两个图像在经过 CNN 的多个层级时会被转换
as they move through several layers of a CNN,
如果你仔细观察
the exact original pixel values matter less and less.
就会发现原始确切像素值越来越不重要
The two transformed outputs should start to look much more similar to one another,
两个转换后的输出应该开始看起来更相似
moving closer towards the idea that both are
然后得出结论：二者都是汽车图像
a car rather than the details about what the cars look like.
而不是关注两个图像里的汽车分别是什么样式和风格的
Later layers in a CNN have discarded information about style and texture,
CNN 中的后续层级丢弃了风格和纹理信息
and instead are pushed towards answering questions about general shape,
而是促使网络去回答一些
and about the presence of unique patterns,
关于一般形状和独特图案的问题
like, "Are there wheels in the image?
例如“图中有车轮吗？”
Are there eyes in the image?
“图中有眼睛吗？”
What about three legs or tails?"
“有三条腿或尾巴吗？”
Once we get to a representation where
一旦我们像这样
the content of an image has been distilled like this,
提取出图像内容后
we can flatten the array into a feature vector and feed it to
我们可以将数组扁平化为特征向量
one or more fully connected layers to determine what object is contained in the image.
然后传入一个或多个全连接层 判断图像中的对象是什么
For instance, if wheels were found after the last max pooling layer,
例如 如果在最后的最大池化层之后发现了轮子
the feature vector will be able to reflect that.
特征向量将能体现这一信息
The fully connected layer will transform that information to
全连接层将转换该信息
predict that a car is present in the image with higher probability.
并以更高的概率预测图中有汽车
If there were eyes, three legs, and a tail,
如果有眼睛 三条腿和尾巴
then the output layer would take that information
那么输出层会考虑该信息
and deduce that a dog is likely present in the image.
并推测图中很可能有一条狗
But of course, to emphasize,
当然要强调下
all this understanding in the model,
模型得出的所有这些结论
is not pre-specified bias.
并不是预先确定的认知
It is learned by the model during training and through back-propagation that
而是模型在训练过程中学习的结果
updates the weights that define
模型会通过反向传播
the filters and the weights in the fully connected layers.
更新定义过滤器的权重及全连接层中的权重
This architecture that we're specifying here just
我们指定的这种结构
gives the model a structure that will allow it to train better.
为模型提供了一种结构 使其能训练得更好
So, it has the potential to classify objects with greater accuracy.
因此它有可能更准确地分类对象
Next, I'll show you how to start defining a CNN architecture for image classification,
接下来我将演示如何开始定义图像分类 CNN 结构
and you'll get to practice coding on your own.
你将有机会练习编写代码